Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records Concerning Community Relations
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records concerning community relations, 1969-1979; Accession 1979-A-014
  - Youth entitlement program, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 89)
- Records concerning community relations, 1970-1980; Accession 1980-A-012
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2015
  - Better Business Bureau, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Black Coalition, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cable TV, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Community Relations, CPAR, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Community relations prize, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Cornucopia, newsletter of the Bronx Venture Corporation, 1973-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Despierta Boricua, the Puerto Rican Student organization at Yale, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - East Haven Public schools, Yale assisted computer curriculum, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Economic development: City Bank proposal, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Economic development: Midtown Motor Inn, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Economic Development Resources, Inc., undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Golf course, 1970-1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Gym privileges, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Holiday Inn, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Hospice, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Latin Youth Leadership Conference, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Lincoln Center Institute, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - MULANEH: Latin American women's organization, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - New Journal, 1973-1978 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Outreach program - Council on East Asian Studies, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Paddock at Yale Field, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Revista, Hispanic literary magazine, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Small business seminar, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Tours, "See New Haven", 1977 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Urban homesteading, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Women's services, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - RESTRICTED (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Admissions, New Haven, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Applications and recommendations for jobs, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Records concerning community relations, 1969-1986; Accession 1987-A-114
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2020
  Scope and Contents
  No online inventory available. Paper inventory available in repository.
  - Accounting-Pending, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ad Campaign, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Data Systems, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Review Committee, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Admissions, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agnelli Exhibit, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Aldermanic Breakfasts, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alderman, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Aldermanic Lunches, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alderman and Mayor, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Area Colleges, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Arts
    - Goals for New Haven, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - New Haven Schools, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Association of Yale Alumni
    - 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 15 - 17)
    - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Association of Yale Alumni Assembly
    - 1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Committee on Continuing Education, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Fall Assembly, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - General, 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - New Haven Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - New Haven/Yale Committee, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Widows, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Athletics
    - 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Football Tickets, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Yale Bowl - Yale-U. Conn. Reception, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Athletic Department, General, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Tennis Camp, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Special Olympics, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Yale Bowl, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Yale Bowl, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 35 - 36)
    - Yale Bowl Films, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Blue Ribbon Commission (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Board of Alderman
    - 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - 1979 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Board of Higher Education
    - 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Report, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Boys and Girls Clubs
    - Community Service Dinner, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Boys' Club Evaluation (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Boys' Club, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Financial Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Boys' Club-Finance Committee, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Boys' Club, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Brooks Committee
    - 1978 (Box 4, Folder 52 - 53)
    - no date (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 55 - 58)
  - Brown University, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Budget
    - 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - IBM Account, 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Cahoon: Internships, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Carcinogens: Legislations, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - C.A.R.P., 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Casa Otonal
    - 1979 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Reports for United Way, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Cedarhurst School, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - CETA Program, 1978-1982 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Education Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Chapel Street, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Chronology: 1st Community Relations Report, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Christ Church Parish, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - City Bank Proposal, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - City Zoning, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Cleveland Conference, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - College Day, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Colleges, New Alternatives, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Combined Health Appeal, 1978-1980 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Commencement
    - 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Commission of Equal Opportunities, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Commission on State Mandates to Cities and Towns, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Committees
    - Association of Yale Alumni, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Building and Grounds Maintenance, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Institutional Policies, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Miscellaneous - Conferences, 1980, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Commons, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Community Relations
    - Annual Reports, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Baldwin Negotiations, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Community and State Relations General, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Discussion Group, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Letters, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Survey, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Community and State, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - 1980 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - 1981 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 105 - 106)
    - State Legislation (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - State Legislators (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Community and State Relations, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Community Relations Policy, 1971-1978 (Box 8, Folder 110 - 111)
  - CONEG, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Connecticut Bipartisan Commission on Tax Return, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Connecticut Conference of Independent Colleges (CCIC) Background, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Connecticut Conference of Municipalities (CCM), 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Connecticut Council on Higher Education
    - 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - By-Laws, Amended, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Memos, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - CT Council for Social Services, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Connecticut Higher Education Loan Authority, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Connecticut Health and Educational Facilities Authority (CHEFA) Legislation, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Connecticut Mental Health Center, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Connecticut Public Radio, Television, 1976-1979 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Connecticut Resources Recovery Authority, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Connecticut State-Miscellaneous, 1977-1984 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - Conntac (Connecticut Talent Assistance Cooperative), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - Contributions
    - Equipment, 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - Financial, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - Miscellaneous, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Requests, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Spanish Community, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - Surplus Furniture, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - Copy Machine, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Council for Urban Economic Development (C.U.E.D), 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - Corporate Research Activities Working Group, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 135)
  - Corporation Counsel Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 136)
  - Crime
    - Crime Committee, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 137)
    - Crime Prevention Program, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - Task Force on Crime, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 139)
  - Cultural Affairs, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 140)
  - "C" Miscellaneous Documents
    - Commission on Higher Education and Economy, 1981 (Box 10)
    - Committee on Labor and Public Employees, 1979 (Box 10)
    - Connecticut Mental Health Center, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Davies House
    - Davies Mansion, 1979-1983 (Box 10, Folder 141)
    - Davies House, 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 142 - 143)
    - Davies House: Special File, 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Day Care
    - Calvin Hill, 1963-1986 (Box 10, Folder 145)
    - General, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 146)
    - Parents Cooperative, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - Phylis Bodel Center, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 148)
    - Reports (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Democratic Platform Committee (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Department of Public Utility Control (DPUC) Southern Connecticut Gas Company, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - DiLieto, Mayor
    - Inauguration, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 152)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 153)
    - Inauguration, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 154)
    - Press Releases, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 155)
    - State of the City Address, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Dining Halls, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - Directions to Yale (by car), undated (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - Dixwell Community House, undated (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - Dixwell Plaza, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - DNA
    - 1977 (Box 12, Folder 161)
    - 1974-1977 (Box 12, Folder 162)
  - Downtown Council: New Haven, 1979-1983 (Box 12, Folder 163 - 164)
  - Downtown Host Program, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 165)
  - Dwight Hall
    - 1981 (Box 12, Folder 166)
    - 1970-1982 (Box 12, Folder 167 - 168)
  - Earthquake, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 169)
  - Economic Development
    - Downtown Development, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 170)
    - Resources, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 171)
    - General, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 172)
    - General, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 173 - 174)
    - 1974-1982 (Box 13, Folder 175 - 176)
    - 1974-1982 (Box 14, Folder 177)
  - Economic Impact Study: Part II, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 178)
  - Edith Wharton Cachets, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 179)
  - Educational Center for the Arts (ECA), 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 180)
  - Education
    - Compensatory, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 181)
    - Continuing, 1971-1981 (Box 14, Folder 182)
    - Employment Hotline, 1979-1983 (Box 14, Folder 183)
    - Non-Traditional Task Force in, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 184)
    - Policy, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Space Program, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 186)
  - Electric Cars, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 187)
  - Elm Ivy/Sterling Scholars Awards, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 188)
  - Employment Requests (OC and SR), 1983 (Box 14, Folder 189)
  - Energy Conservation, 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 190)
  - Energy Week, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 191)
  - Ensemble Company, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 192)
  - Environmental Protection Act, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 193)
  - Ethics Commission
    - 1979 (Box 15, Folder 194 - 195)
    - 1982 (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Connecticut State, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 197)
  - Equal Access, Equal Opportunity, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 198)
  - Events, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 199)
  - "Facts About Yale", 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 200)
  - Faculty Club, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 201)
  - Fair Haven Parents Ministry, Incorporated, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 202)
  - Federal Relations, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 203)
  - Federal Student Aid, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 204)
  - Finance and Administration, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 205)
  - Financial Ledger, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 206)
  - Financial Statement, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 207)
  - Fitness
    - Golf Course, 1978-1982 (Box 15, Folder 208)
    - ITAA Golf Tournament Independent Insurance Agents of America, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 209)
  - Foreman Committee
    - Background, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 210)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 211)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1978 May 5 (Box 16, Folder 212)
    - Foreman Committee and Draft, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 213)
    - Meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 214)
    - Report, Final, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 215)
    - Foreman Report: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 216)
  - Fuel Task Force, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 217)
  - Gateway Landing, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 219)
  - General Assembly
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 220)
    - Internships, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 221)
    - Property Tax Study, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 222)
  - General Correspondence, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 223)
  - General Counsel, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 224)
  - Giamatti, A. Bartlett
    - Correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 17, Folder 225 - 227)
    - Development letters, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 228)
    - Dinner, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 229)
    - Inauguration, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 230)
    - Speeches, 1978-1981 (Box 17, Folder 231)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 232)
  - Goals
    - 1977 (Box 17, Folder 233)
    - 1977 (Box 18, Folder 234)
    - Planning, 1977-1981 (Box 18, Folder 235 - 237)
  - Governance Commission, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 238)
  - Grant Program, Ulysses S.
    - 1978-1980 (Box 18, Folder 240)
    - pre-1978 (Box 18, Folder 241)
    - pre-1978 (Box 19, Folder 242)
  - Greetings on the Green, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 243)
  - Guide to New Haven Neighborhoods, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 244)
  - Halcyon, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 245)
  - Harbor, 1977-1982 (Box 19, Folder 247)
  - Hartford City Council and Tax, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 249)
  - Hamill Proposal, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 250)
  - Harrison Reception, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 251)
  - Health Plan, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 252)
  - Heritage Hall
    - 1979-1982 (Box 19, Folder 253 - 254)
    - Development Corporation, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 255)
  - High School Program, 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 256)
  - Hill Health Center
    - 1970-1980 (Box 20, Folder 257)
    - Hill-West Haven Health Center, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 258)
  - Historic Preservation
    - 1978-1981 (Box 20, Folder 259)
    - Connecticut Trust for, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 260)
    - General, 1976-1980 (Box 20, Folder 261)
    - National Trust Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 262)
    - National District, 1980-1985 (Box 20, Folder 263)
  - Hockey, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 264)
  - Home Health Care, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 265)
  - Home Maintenance Corporation, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 266)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 267)
  - Hospice, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 268)
  - Howard Hughes Medical, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 269)
  - Human Resources Administration, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 270)
  - Inauguration, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 271)
  - Institute for Social and Policy Studies, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 272)
  - Instrument Transplant, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 273)
  - Inter-Department Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 274)
  - Inter Office Correspondence (Clerical), 1983-1986 (Box 20, Folder 275)
  - Internships - Yale, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 276)
  - Jaycees, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 278)
  - Jewish Community Center, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 279)
  - Jobs for America's Graduates, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 280)
  - Job Requests, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 281)
  - Kiosks, 1972-1979 (Box 21, Folder 282)
  - Labor Negotiations
    - Strike, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 283)
    - 1977 (Box 21, Folder 284)
  - Lee, Richard C., 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 285)
  - Legal Assistance Association, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 286)
  - Legislation
    - 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 287)
    - 1981 (Box 21, Folder 288)
    - 1982 (Box 21, Folder 289 - 290)
    - Enacted 1980: Wrap-up and Memos (Box 21, Folder 292)
    - General, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 293)
    - General, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 294)
    - Hospitals and Health Care, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 295)
    - Memos, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 296)
    - Midwives, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 297)
    - New Haven Package, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 298)
    - Open Testing, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 299)
    - Retirement-CCIC Memos (CT Conference of Independent Colleges), 1979 (Box 22, Folder 300)
    - Retirement: House and Senate Action, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 301)
    - Retirement: Public Hearing and Committee, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 302)
    - Tax Issues, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 303)
    - Truth in Testing, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 304)
    - Yale Liquor Bill, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 305)
    - Legislature, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 306)
  - Library
    - Privileges, 1976-1978 (Box 22, Folder 307)
    - Public Building, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 308)
    - Seeley Mudd, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 309)
    - Storage Project, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 310)
  - Low Level Waste
    - 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 317)
    - 1982 (Box 23, Folder 318)
  - Manpower, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 319)
  - Media, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 321)
  - Memos from Secretary's Office (Box 23, Folder 322)
  - Minority Organizations, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 323)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 324)
  - Multiple Sclerosis, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 325)
  - Music, School of, Woolsey Hall, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 326)
  - Music Center, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 327)
  - Nova (National Organization for Victim Assistance), 1980 (Box 23, Folder 328)
  - National Preservation
    - New Haven, 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 329)
    - Prospect Hill District, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 330)
  - Neighborhood Housing, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 331)
  - New Careers for Women, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 332)
  - New Haven
    - City of, Miscellaneous, 1980-1984 (Box 24, Folder 333)
    - City of, News Releases, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 334)
    - City of, Police horses, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 335)
    - Positive Propoganda, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 336)
    - Street Law Project, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 337)
    - Preservation Trust, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 338)
    - Convention and Visitors Bureau, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 339)
  - North Haven Mall, 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 340)
  - Olin Corporation, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 341)
  - Papero Youth Association, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 342)
  - Peabody Museum, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 343 - 344)
  - Pearce H., Company, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 345)
  - People Acting for Change (PAC), 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 346)
  - Personnel Department
    - Inter-office Correspondence, 1972-1982 (Box 25, Folder 347)
    - Payroll, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 348)
  - Photography, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 349)
  - Physical Development Project, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 350)
  - Polling, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 351)
  - Policy Committee on Electronic Communication, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 352)
  - Posters, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 353)
  - Princeton University, 1970-1977 (Box 25, Folder 354)
  - Project More, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 355)
  - Projects with Industry, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 356)
  - Property
    - Alpha, General (Box 25, Folder 357)
    - Alpha, Mansfield and Prospect Streets, 1979-1982 (Box 25, Folder 358)
    - Alpha, Prospect Hill District, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 359)
    - Sterling Nursing Dormitory, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 360)
    - Alpha, Trinity Church Parish House, 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 361)
    - Alpha, Western Parimeter (Box 25, Folder 362)
    - General, 1978-1982 (Box 26, Folder 363)
    - General, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 364)
    - New Haven, Lake Place, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 365)
    - New Haven, Broadway Areas, 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 366)
    - New Haven, Maretz-Franford Realtors, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 367)
    - New Haven, Church and Chapel Streets, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 368)
    - New Haven, Park Street, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 369)
    - New Haven, Edwards Street #360, 1978-1980 (Box 26, Folder 370)
    - New Haven, Elm Street #149, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 371)
    - New Haven, Eldorado Apartments, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 372)
    - New Haven, Faculty Club, undated (Box 26, Folder 373)
    - New Haven, Forest Road, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 374)
    - New Haven, Grove Street Park, 1975-1979 (Box 26, Folder 375)
    - New Haven, Hart Investment Company, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 376)
    - New Haven, Horse Island, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 377)
    - New Haven, Knights of St. Patrick's, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 378)
    - New Haven, Old Campus, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 379)
    - New Haven, Park Plaza, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 380)
    - Problems (Box 26, Folder 381)
  - Proposed Yale Operating Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 382)
  - Publications: Other Colleges
    - 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 383)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 384 - 385)
  - Public Relations, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 386)
  - Public Schools: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 387)
  - Public Utility Control Authority (PUCA), 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 388)
  - Purchasing
    - Correspondence, 1969-1981 (Box 27, Folder 389)
    - Office Furniture Standards, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 390)
    - Minority Contracting (Box 27, Folder 391)
  - "Q'' Fever, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 392)
  - Racial Sensitivity Group, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 393)
  - "Radiation Safety at Yale", 1977 (Box 27, Folder 394)
  - Railroad Station, 1977-1979 (Box 27, Folder 395)
  - Real Estate Advisory Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 27, Folder 396 - 397)
  - Red Cross, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 398)
  - Redevelopment, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 399)
  - Requests for Use of Yale Facilities, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 400)
  - Retirement: Yale Report on Policy, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 401)
  - Revenue Commission (Box 27, Folder 402)
  - Rockware International-New Haven, City of, 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 403)
  - Rockwell International-Hartford National, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 404)
  - Russian Chorus, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 405)
  - St. Raphael's Hospital, 1981-1985 (Box 28, Folder 406)
  - Salaries, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 407)
  - Schiavone Development, 1979-1982 (Box 28, Folder 408)
  - Science Park
    - 1983 (Box 28, Folder 409)
    - Development, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 410 - 411)
    - Development, 1981-1983 (Box 28, Folder 412 - 414)
  - Secretary's Office, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 415)
  - Security Committee
    - 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 416)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 417)
  - Security, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 418)
  - Shubert Theater, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 419)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 420)
  - Southern Connecticut Gas Company, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 421)
  - Southern Connecticut Telephone Company (Box 29, Folder 422)
  - South Central Community College, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 423 - 424)
  - Special Assistant
    - Memos to Sam Chauncy, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 425)
    - Tasks, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 426)
  - Sports
    - Schiavone Sports Board Meeting, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 427)
    - U.S. Youth Games, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 428)
  - State Investment Policies, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 429)
  - State Legislation, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 430)
  - State Street, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 431)
  - Stauffer Chemical Company, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 432)
  - Street System, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 436)
  - Student Guide to New Haven
    - 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 437)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 438)
  - Studies, Miscellaneous